人人影视
原创翻译  双语字幕
字幕组招新中
请访问 YYSubs.com
翻译    苏葵
校对    苏葵
时间轴    壬虚浪影
后期    渔夫
总监    苏葵
在我们死之前
第三集
碧昂卡
Bianca.
发生什么了吗
Has something happened?
不  我...
No. I...
我想跟你谈谈
..I hoped we could talk?
斯特凡跟你在一起吗
Is Stefan with you?
请我进去吧
Invite me in then.
你想来点吗
Oh, do you want some?
-不  -抱歉
- No. - Sorry.
我知道麦当娜红酒餐厅绝不会卖这种垃圾
I know they'd never sell crap like this at Vino Modana.
不不  有时离开餐厅也挺好
No, no, it's nice to get away from the restaurant sometimes.
我们可以不在那边
I mean, we can talk properly for one thing
好好谈谈  所以
when we're not there, so...
我其实想跟你谈谈
I wanted to talk to you, actually.
行
Sure.
是关于斯特凡
It's Stefan, it's...
不  我理解
Oh, no, I understand.
不是
No, um...
我四岁时就认识他了
..I've known him since I was four.
我  我妈妈  达沃  我们
Me, my mum, Davor, we're...
-我们是他唯一的家人  -嗯
- ..We're all he's got. - Yeah.
没事  你不用跟我解释什么
It's OK, you don't need to explain anything.
不
No, um...
从我记事以来
..We've been destined to be together
我们就已经订亲了  而且
for as long as I can remember and...
我很在乎他
..I really care for him.
但他不是我每天醒来
But he's not the person I wake up
和睡前想念的人
and go to bed thinking about.
碧昂卡  这个
Bianca, it's...
碧昂卡  我不
Bianca, I'm not...
桑姬塔
Hello, Sangita.
见鬼  比利  一周两次
Fuck me, Billy, twice in a week?
别担心  你可以黑进英格兰银行
Don't worry, you can be hacking the Bank of England,
我也不在乎
for all I care.
这次你想要什么
So, what do you want this time?
我上周刚帮你黑进去这个
I hacked this for you last week.
我需要你大大加强它的加密
I need you to massively strengthen its encryption,
让任何试图打开它的人都头疼
make it nigh on impossible for anyone to access.
你能做到吗
Can you do that?
还有一件事
And one more thing...
我要你帮我创建一个新账户
I need you to create me a new ID.
-克里斯申  -米密查太太
- Christian. - Mrs Mimica.
叫我杜布拉芙卡
Dubravka, please.
达沃让我过来
Davor asked me to come.
当然  他在阳台
Of course, he's on the terrace.
你家真漂亮
You have an amazing home.
你第一次来吗
Your first time here?
我希望之后还有很多次
I hope the first of many.
他们收到信息了吗
非常清楚
他们很清楚自己会发生什么
他们知道会得到什么  以及惹怒我们会失去什么
我们会搞死他们
我们吗
怎么回事
What was that?
我想你妈妈打碎了什么
I think your mum dropped something.
去看看她是否需要帮忙
Go and see if she needs help.
那孩子还以为自己是黑帮呢
Ah, the kid thinks he's a gangster.
-我们有个工作给你  -好
- We have a job for you. - Sure.
我们需要你租一艘船  快船
We need you to rent a boat, a fast one,
能容纳四个人
big enough for four people.
至少能开六百英里
Range of at least 600 miles.
你什么时候需要
And when do you need it?
尽快
Soon as possible.
你没有问题吗
Don't you have any questions?
如果需要我知道  你会告诉我
If I need to know, you'll tell me.
有些事你该知道  老地方见
六百英里
600 miles?
那可能是任何地方
That could be bloody anywhere.
他们没说其他事吗
And they didn't say anything else?
就这些
That was it.
他们没说还是你没问
They didn't say or you didn't ask?
我不想引起怀疑
I didn't want to raise suspicions.
你不能总打安全牌
You can't always play it safe.
这是他的决定  比利  不是你的
That's his call, Billy, not yours.
我要给船装监听器
I'm going to have to bug the cabin.
-当然  -这是个好主意吗
- Of course. - Is that a good idea?
你知道这种事的套路
You know how this works.
我们需要铁证  否则就是捕风捉影
We need hard evidence or we're pissing in the wind.
不  太危险了
Nah, it's too dangerous.
这整个行动都很危险
The whole fucking shebang is dangerous.
你在冒险这事上没有独断专权  比利
You don't have the monopoly on risk-taking, Billy!
我们都想抓到这群畜生
We all want to catch these fuckers,
只是不会不顾一切
just not at any cost.
我以为你说自己不会牵扯进来
I thought you said you weren't going to be involved?
我打算去码头
I'm going to head down to the marina,
问问价格  知道个大概
shop around, get some estimates.
-怎么了  -你有掩饰身份的说辞吗
- What? - Have you got a cover story?
什么
A what?
如果有人看到你来这  你打算怎么说
You know, what you say if someone sees you coming here.
-你有吗  -见鬼了  别烦我
- Well? - For fuck's sake, stop nagging me.
我只是想保护你
I'm just trying to protect you.
你现在表现地像我妈
Well, you're behaving like my mother.
圣尼古拉斯市场
你在跟踪我吗
Are you following me?
我只是闹着玩
I was just messing around.
你来这里干什么
What are you doing in this part of town?
我有事要办
I just had stuff to do.
什么事
What stuff?
家里事  你知道的
Family shit, you know.
不  克里斯申  我不知道
No, Christian, I don't know.
-抱歉  我无意...  -我开玩笑的
- Sorry, I didn't mean... - I'm kidding, forget it.
拜托
Come on.
谢了
Thanks.
那你呢
So, what about you?
我过来见一个跟我赌注有关的人
I've been meeting a guy about my bet.
你的赌注
Your bet?
对  我跟你说的那个
Yeah, you know, the one I told you about.
篮球比赛吗
Oh, the basketball game?
不是普通比赛  克里斯申  是欧洲杯
It's not just a game, Christian, it's a European Cup match.
如果十字军球队能赢超过三分
And if the Crusaders win by three points or more...
我就能赚八万
..I'll make 80 grand.
什么
What?
他们的对手是谁
Well, who are they playing?
去年的亚军
Last year's runners-up.
我以为英国人不擅长篮球
I thought us Brits weren't very good at basketball.
确实
We're not.
那听上去希望不大
It sounds like a long shot then.
除非比赛被操控了
Not if the game is rigged.
你要怎么操纵篮球比赛
How the fuck did you rig a basketball game?
-你也下注吗  -好啊
- Are you in? - Yeah.
好  我去弄点现金
Yeah, let me rustle up some cash.
我们比赛之后开派对
We'll party after the game.
他不像我想象的那样
没人会听到我们  妈  你可以说英语
No-one's going to hear us, Mum. You can speak English.
我想给她找个更好的人
I wanted better for her.
比什么更好
Better than what?
斯特凡
Stefan.
他就快成为我们中的一员了
He's about to become one of us.
他是个傻瓜
He's a fool.
你想让我叫停吗
Do you want me to put a stop to it?
我应该开心
I should be happy.
至少我有个孩子能结婚
At least one of my children will be married.
我得走了
I have to go.
你要去哪见他
Where are you meeting him?
老地方
The usual place.
别再让我等了
Don't keep me waiting again.
你说得对  我需要一个说辞
You were right. I need a cover story.
为什么  发生了什么吗
Why? Has something happened?
斯特凡举止奇怪
Stefan's acting weird.
我们该担心吗
Should we be worried?
达沃
Davor...
有人刚好有我们餐厅的照片吗
..Somebody just happens to leave the picture of our restaurant
放在警局的复印机上
lying on the photocopier of the police station?
那是上次调查的照片
It's from the previous investigation.
或其他人接手了
Or someone else has taken over
那个死警察的调查
where the dead cop left off.
你听到了  谋杀案调查毫无进展
You heard it, the murder investigation is going nowhere.
我还听说或许有其他团队在调查
I heard also there may be other teams working on it...
但我们的线人并不知道
..That our source doesn't know about.
我去处理
I'll take care of it.
很好  你们都在
Good, you're all here.
我有事告诉你们
I have something to tell you.
说吧
Go ahead.
我觉得有人在给警察提供消息
I think someone is feeding information to the police.
你为什么现在才告诉我们
Why are you just telling us this now?
我刚发现
I just found out.
达沃  拜托
Davor, please.
我们听着呢  斯特凡
Yes, we're listening, Stefan.
好
OK, so...
你要找什么类型的船
So what exactly are you looking for?
能开六百英里
Something that can do 600 miles.
好  所有船都有标配的绘图机
OK, well, they all come standard with chart plotting,
船头和艉侧推器
bow and stern thrusters.
你打算什么时候租
So when are you looking to rent?
尽快吧
As soon as possible, really.
-好  -抱歉  稍等
- OK. - Um, sorry, just one second.
达沃
Hey, Davor.
-你在哪  -在码头
- Where are you? - At the marina.
回来  我要看看你找到了什么
Head back. I want to see what you found.
我才刚到
I only just got here.
无所谓  快回来
Doesn't matter, come - now.
没听到你离开
Didn't hear you leave.
我得回去了
I needed to get back.
有人跟你在一起吗
Is someone there with you?
有
Er, yeah.
家里出什么事了吗
Is something going on at the house?
没有
No.
有什么我该担心的吗
Nothing I should worry about?
我想没有
I don't think so.
达沃的举止怪异吗
And Davor isn't acting weird?
不  我想我们不需要什么
No, no, I don't think we need anything.
纸巾
Napkins.
能给我们带点纸巾吗
Could you pick us up some napkins?
好
Ok.
好  那我们一会见
Yes, I guess I'll see you in a bit.
好
Ok.
达沃让我回去了
Davor's called me in.
-什么事  -他没说
- What about? - He didn't say.
别慌
Don't panic.
有人吗
Hello?
在厨房
In the kitchen.
你个天使
You angel.
达沃在健身房
Davor's in the fitness room.
停下
Stop.
停停停
Stop, stop, stop.
这是怎么回事
What's this about?
你认得这地方吗
Do you recognise this place...
或这个女人吗
..Or this woman?
我能问问你为什么这样审问我吗
Am I allowed to ask why you're questioning me like this?
别装无辜
Don't act innocent.
斯特凡说你一直
Stefan says you've been...
在跟这个女人见面
..Meeting with this woman.
她是个警察
And she's a fucking cop.
H·莱恩女士
Ms H Laing.
海伦·莱恩
Helen Laing?
瞧  我告诉你了
See? I told you.
是真的吗
So it's true?
她是我妈妈
Well, she's my mum.
你母亲是个警察
Your mother is a cop?
不
No.
她是个会计
She's an accountant.
那是个谎言  给他看
That's a fucking lie. Show him.
西南警局
-她有个朋友在那工作  -瞎说
- Well, she has a friend that works there. - Bullshit.
她只是个前台  或许他们一起吃午餐了
She's just a receptionist. Maybe they had lunch or something.
这个女人叫什么
What's this woman's name?
她叫什么
What's her name?
玛丽安
Marianne.
玛丽安·杰克森
Marianne Jackson.
把他的手机给我
Give me his phone.
解锁
Open it.
克里斯申  生快  汉娜  祝你今天开心
汉娜·莱恩  谢了  克里斯
克里斯
Chrissy?
是你吗
Is that you?
-海伦·莱恩吗  -是我
- Helen Laing? - Yes.
我是杜布拉芙卡·米密查
Dubravka Mimica.
怎么了
Yes?
-我能进来吗  -我正要出去
- Can I come in? - Er, well, I... I was just on my way out.
不会耽误很久
It won't take a moment.
请进吧
Come on through.
地方不错  你住在这里吗
Nice place. Do you live here?
不  我住在雷德兰
No, Redland.
肯定花了你不少钱
It must cost you a fortune.
我离婚时分到的
I... I got it in my divorce.
从克里斯申父亲那吗
From Christian's father?
不好意思
Sorry?
不  我才该不好意思
No, it's me who should be sorry.
我没好好介绍自己
I didn't introduce myself properly.
我是克里斯申的老板
I'm Christian's boss.
他又干什么了
What's he done now?
什么也没做
Nothing.
他干得很好
He's doing great.
那他推荐我了吗
So, has he recommended me?
推荐你
Recommended you?
你不是在找会计吗
Well, you are looking for an accountant?
天呐  不是  我刚好在附近  就想过来
God, no. I was in the neighbourhood and thought I'd come
介绍介绍自己  邀请你吃个饭
and introduce myself, invite you for a meal.
那太好了
That would be fantastic.
我听说你家餐馆很棒
I've heard your restaurant is amazing.
我是说去我家
I mean at my home.
家庭晚宴
A family dinner.
你真好心  但我得问问克里斯申
That's very kind, erm, but I'll need to check with Christian.
当然
Of course.
好
Ok.
你真是让人失望
You're just such a disappointment.
什么
What?
-不可能  -兹沃诺
- No way. - Zvono!
海伦·莱恩  会计师
任何人都能伪造网页
Anyone can fake a web page.
他还给警局打电话了
He also phoned the police station.
猜猜谁在接线处工作
And guess who is working on the switchboard?
去外面等着
Go and wait outside.
我欠你个道歉
I owe you an apology.
小心驶得万年船
You can't be too careful.
这...
It's...
我不理解斯特凡为什么会说你告密
I don't understand why Stefan would point the finger at you.
或许他觉得我威胁了他在这个家庭的地位
Maybe he thinks I'm muscling in on his place in the family.
跟我说实话  克里斯申
Tell me the truth, Christian.
他觉得我爱上碧昂卡了
He thinks I'm in love with Bianca.
你有吗
Are you?
你在跟我妹妹上床吗
Are you fucking my sister?
我没那么蠢
I'm not that stupid.
给你  克里斯
Here you go, Chrissy.
你去吧
Here you go.
像个爷们
Take it like a man.
妈的
Fuck!
听我说  听我说
Listen to me... Listen to me!
别耍小聪明
Don't try to be smart.
你去跟克里斯申和好  听懂没
You make it up with Christian, you understand?
你今天躲过一劫
You dodged a bullet today.
-谢天谢地有玛丽安·杰克森  -对  很不错
- Thank God for Marianne Jackson. - Yeah, that was a nice touch.
我们得再小心点
We just have to be more careful.
-我要停止你们的行动  -不行
- I'm shutting you down. - No!
我们刚有点起色
We're starting to get somewhere.
听着  是我在冒险
Look, it's my neck on the line.
这不是正式批准的调查  克里斯申
This isn't an officially sanctioned investigation, Christian.
我们所有人都在冒险
All our necks are on the line.
拜托  再给点时间
Please, just let it play out a little longer.
我已经给了你时间
I've already given you time.
他用来获取可被法庭采纳的证据了
Which he's used to acquire admissible evidence
用来证明一项重大犯罪阴谋
on a major criminal conspiracy.
我很确定凯恩警司
Which I'm sure Superintendent Kane
会为此感恩
will be hugely grateful for.
我不离开餐厅
I'm not leaving the restaurant.
-克里斯申  -我不走
- Christian. - I'm not!
直到我们能证明跟肖恩有关
Not until we prove the link to Sean.
听着
Look...
我跟你们一样
..I want to catch these scumbags
-也想抓住他们  -那就证明啊
- as much as you do. - Then prove it.
给我们一点时间
Give us some time.
我们已经很接近了
Look, we're really close.
达沃开始接纳我了
Davor's letting me in.
72小时
72 hours...
找到联系
..To find the link.
之后我就要过去
After that, I'm coming down there
把你拖出来  亲自逮捕你
to drag you out and arrest you myself.
我需要再来一瓶啤酒
Well, that calls for a beer.
-怎么这么久  -我今早才拿到
- What's taking so long? - I was only given it this morning.
我们都等了一周了
We've been waiting almost a week.
你们或许得再多等一阵  伙计
And you might be waiting a lot longer than that, mate.
-什么意思  -这东西的加密程度
- How do you mean? - Level of encryption on this.
就像恩尼格玛密码机一样
It's like the sodding Enigma code.
欢迎  请进
Welcome. Come in.
-这些给你  -谢谢
- These are for you. - Oh, thank you.
-这是我儿子  -很高兴终于见面了
- This is my son. - It's so nice to finally meet you.
-我是达沃  -我也很幸会  我是海伦
- I'm Davor. - Very nice to meet you, too. I'm Helen.
约万  我侄子
Jovan, my nephew.
-你好  约万  侄子  你好  -你好
- Hello, Jovan, the nephew. Hello. - Hi.
这是我女儿  碧昂卡
This is my daughter, Bianca.
你好  很高兴认识你
Oh, hello. Very nice to meet you.
-欢迎  -谢谢
- Welcome. - Thank you.
还有斯特凡  她未婚夫
And Stefan, her fiance.
-你好吗  -欢迎
- Hi. How are you? - Welcome.
-约万  帮海伦拿外套  -非常感谢
- Jovan, take Helen's coat, please. - Thank you very much.
-我能帮你拿吗  -好
- Can I get yours? - Yeah, yeah.
-外面有点冷  -这边走
- It's a bit chilly out there. - This way.
谢谢  房子真美
Thank you. What a lovely house.
看着好美味
This looks delicious.
-你在厨房忙了一天吧  -一整天
- Have you been in the kitchen all day? - All day.
向来如此
Always.
克里斯申告诉我你前夫是克罗地亚人
So, Christian tells me your ex-husband is from Croatia.
对  但他在这里
Yes, but he's lived here for
生活了三十年  所以
the best part of 30 years, so...
一日克罗地亚人  永远克罗地亚魂  对吧
You never stop being Croatian, right?
我想没人跟尼克说过这个
Well, I'm not sure that anyone's told Nick that.
-你去过那里吗  海伦  -克罗地亚吗  去过
- Have you been there, Helen? - To Croatia? Yeah.
对  克里斯申小时候去度过几次假
Yeah, a couple of times on holiday when Christian was small.
-你们去哪了  -我们去了小岛  哈瓦
- Where did you go? - Oh, we went to an island. Havar.
那里叫哈瓦尔
It's pronounced Hvar.
哈瓦尔  哈瓦尔吗
Hvar? Hvar?
-我说得对吗  -对  完美
- Is that right? - Yeah. Perfect.
哈瓦尔  我们去了哈瓦尔
Hvar. We went to Hvar.
-你喜欢那里吗  -超爱
- And did you like it? - Yes, loved it.
美如仙境
Absolutely beautiful.
但有一个假期  克里斯申
But there was one holiday when Christian
-非常害怕  -害怕
- got absolutely terrified. - Terrified?
对  有一种林鸽
Yeah. There were these wood pigeons
克里斯申觉得它们的叫声像狼
and Christian thought that they sounded like wolves.
-真可爱  -是啊
- How adorable. - Yeah.
-他那个年龄肯定很好看  -确实  确实
- I bet he was gorgeous at that age. - Yeah, he was, he was.
-他就是个妈宝  -妈  别说了
- He was a real mummy's boy. - Mum, stop.
真的吗  妈宝  但你从没去监狱探望过他
Really? Mummy's boy? But you never visited him in jail.
斯特凡  你在侮辱我们的客人
Stefan, you are insulting our guest.
不
No.
不不  没关系
No, no, no, it's OK.
我  我不否认当时我觉得很丢脸
I... I don't mind admitting I was ashamed of him.
但我现在不是了
But I'm not now.
自从他跟你们在一起
Ever since he's been with you,
自从他来到你们的餐厅  我...
ever since he's been in your restaurant, I...
我说不出自己有多骄傲
I can't tell you how proud of him I am.
敬家人
To family.
我很抱歉我们怀疑了你
I'm sorry we doubted you.
没必要
There's really no need.
我不该听他的
I shouldn't have listened to him.
换了我也会这么做
I would have done the same.
我们认为有人在给警察
We believe someone is supplying information
提供我们的信息
to the police about us.
家里人吗
Someone in the family?
或熟人
Or close to it.
我猜他忍不住
I suppose he hasn't been able to
炫耀克拉伊纳的事
resist boasting about Krajina.
他跟我说了一些
He's told me a little.
现在你知道我们为什么要额外警觉  甚至多疑
Now you know why we need to be extra vigilant. Paranoid even.
当然
Of course.
那会让我们非常富裕
It is going to make us very rich.
我们所有人
All of us.
包括你
You included.
你以前杀过人吗
Have you ever killed anyone?
但你觉得你能行吗
But do you think you could?
我想不行
I don't think so.
我想你会让自己惊讶的
I think you're going to surprise yourself.
杀人只需要勇气
All it takes is character...
而你有很多
..And you have plenty of that.
这只是说说
Look, it's just talk.
他在获取情报  仅此而已
He's marking his card, that's all.
让他知道他们是认真的
Letting him know they mean business.
看这个
Here, look at this.
-那是他们要租的船吗  -对
- Is that the boat they're hiring? - Aye.
之前是渔船
Ex-fishing charter.
航行过几次  但状态依旧很好
Done a few knots, but still in good nick.
我应该能在那块板后面
I should be able to plant the listening device
装上监听器
behind that panel there.
很高科技
Pretty high-tech.
-Q最近很忙啊  -对
- Q has been busy. - Aye.
运动激活的录音监听设备
Motion activated recording and listening device.
不是买一送一的标准警察监听破烂
None of your buy-one-get-one-free standard issue police crap.
如果你拿不到上好的监听器
Well, you wouldn't be much of a spook
那你也算不上什么好间谍
if you couldn't get your mitts on a decent listening device,
比利  是不是
Billy, would you now?
有东西吗
Anything?
没问题
It's clean.
那么
So...
我们和好了
..We're cool?
嗯  和好了  斯特凡
Yeah, we're cool, Stefan.
很好  因为我需要你帮忙
Good, because I need your help.
你记得我说能赢八万的那场篮球赛吧
You remember I stand to win 80 grand on this basketball game?
这数字可不容易忘
It's not a number you forget.
我想或许
Well, I thought maybe...
我们可以用这钱来干个买卖
..We could use it to set up shop together.
你和我吗
Me and you?
我得开始自立门户  达沃生我气了
I need to start doing my own shit. Davor is pissed with me.
如果他发现我们在他的地盘上贩毒
He's going to be even more pissed
那他会更加生气
if we start dealing on his patch.
-不不  我不是说那些  -那是什么
- No, no, I'm not talking about that shit. - What, then?
开庄赌球
Spread betting on sports.
如果你找到办法操纵比赛  能大赚一笔
You can make a fortune if you find a way to fix the games.
你从没告诉我是怎么干的
Well, you never told me how that's done.
简单
Easy.
你给队员分成
You cut the players in
然后威胁如果他不照你说的做
and then you threaten to kill their family
就杀了他们全家
if they don't come through.
-最近的比赛就是这样吗  -对
- Is that's what's happening with this latest game? - Yeah.
飞翼队的一个队员是我的人
One of the players for the Wings is my guy.
那很有用
That's useful.
我们真的知道他妻子住哪里
We really do know where his wife lives.
你可以帮忙确保她收到消息
You can help make sure she gets the message.
让我想想  可以吗
Let me think about it, yeah?
可以
Sure.
我理解
I get it.
你得想清楚是否该再信任我
You need to work out whether you should trust me again.
就像我得想清楚我是否该再次信任你
Just like I've needed to work out whether I should trust you.
我以为这事已经解决了
I thought we sorted that.
谢谢
Thanks.
听着  我看到你看碧昂卡的眼神了
Look, I've seen the way you look at Bianca.
-斯特凡  我...  -没事
- Stefan, I... - It's alright.
你什么都不用说  我不傻
You don't have to say anything. I'm not stupid.
但如果你真是我的朋友
But if you really are my friend...
那你就知道我有多爱她
..Then you know how much I love her.
我想纹个碧昂卡  但太疼了
I wanted to write Bianca, but it hurt too much.
-你个疯子  -你闭上嘴
- You nutter! - Keep your mouth shut.
不能告诉任何人
You can't say this to anyone.
笑死
Oh, fuck.
干杯
Cheers.
你个蠢货  你说不够是什么意思
You dumb bastard! What do you mean it's not enough?
我  我不能失去职业
Well, I... I could lose my career.
或更重要的东西
Or something more important.
你不用威胁我
You don't need to threaten me.
听着  这只是开始
Look, this is just the start.
我们能一起变富裕
We're going to get rich together,
砰砰砰  这没事
bop, bop, bop, which is cool.
他们输三分或以上
They lose by three or more.
三分或以上
Three or more.
我们该走了
We should go.
淡定
Be cool.
-我会看着的  -好
- I'll be watching. - Sure.
比利
Billy.
你知道他们会回来
You knew they'd come back.
你自己也知道  他们很多疑
You know yourself, they're paranoid.
达沃相信我
Davor trusts me.
他谁都不相信
He trusts no-one.
他开始告诉我一些事了
He's starting to tell me things.
别自满
Don't get complacent.
走错一步
One false move...
你就死定了
..And you're dead meat.
别低估他们
Don't underestimate them...
任何人
..Any of them...
兹沃诺密尔  杜布拉芙卡  斯特凡
..Zvonomir, Dubravka, Stefan.
达沃想摆脱斯特凡
Davor wants rid of Stefan.
或许我们能推他一把
Maybe we could give him a wee shove?
我该当作没看到吗
Shall I pretend I didn't see that?
对
Yeah.
谢谢这个
Hey, thanks for that.
他们来了
Ah, here they are!
这真是个超绝妙的单身派对
What a great idea for a stag night.
这是达沃的主意  不是我的
It was Davor's, not mine.
-还单身派对  更像是悲伤派对  -有什么好笑的
- More like a sad night than a stag night. - What's the joke?
有什么好笑的
What's the joke?
你最好笑
You are the joke.
已经落后六分了
Six points behind, already.
闭嘴
Oh, shut up.
别这样  老兄  我就是逗你
Come on, man, I'm just teasing.
你觉得怎么样
What do you reckon?
来啊
Come on, yeah.
-棒  -不
- Yeah! - No!
我觉得你的人没收到信息  斯特凡
I don't think your guys have got the message, Stefan.
妈的
Fuck!
他们最好别耍我
They better not screw with me.
-无论发生什么  -什么
- Whatever happens... - What?
我们别管他们了
..Let's blow them off.
我们去玩吧  就你和我
Let's go and party together, just the two of us.
看情况吧
We'll see.
-妈的  -赞啊
- Fuck! - Yes.
妈的
Fuck!
我要下去看
I'm going down there.
真的吗
Seriously?
我得让他看到我是认真的
I need to show I mean business.
太好了
Yeah!
搞什么
What the fuck?
那家伙是警察
比利  你他妈在干什么
你还接受下赌吗
Hey, are you still taking bets?
该死的叛徒
Fucking snitch...
斯特凡
..Stefan.
我认识你吗
Do I know you from somewhere?
我是杰米的朋友
I'm a friend of Jamie's.
多少钱
How much?
五百成吗  伙计
Can you do 500, pal?
怎么  他们认识吗
What, they know each other?
对  他们认识
Yeah, they know each other.
加油  加油
Come on, come on.
-你做到了  你做到了  -我做到了
- You did it, you did it! - I fucking did it!
来吧  豪华轿车在等着
Come on, limo is waiting.
豪华轿车
Limo?
我现在暂时无法接电话
Oh, I can't come to the phone at the moment,
请留言
so leave a message.
他们要杀了他
They're going to kill him.
八万块
80 fucking grand!
满上  满上
Up, up, up, up.
你要去哪
Hey, where are you going?
没事  计划有变
It's OK, change of plan.
但今天属于我
But this is my day.
当然  当然
Of course, of course.
我们为你准备了惊喜
We have something for you.
兹沃诺密尔
Zvonomir!
干杯
干杯  干杯
私人派对  私人派对
Private, private.
达沃
Davor!
我说了吧
I told you.
今天属于你
Today is your day.
我们给你准备了小惊喜
We have a little surprise for you.
她在哪
Where is she, huh?
克里斯申呢
Where's Christian?
紧急情况  请问您需要什么服务
Emergency, which service do you require?
警察
The police.
来吧
Come.
来吧  来吧
Come, come.
搞什么
What the fuck?
搞什么  搞什么
What the fuck? What the fuck?
达沃
Davor?
Davor...
怎么回事
..What's happening?
这就是我们中的叛徒  克里斯申
There's our informer, Christian.
不可能
No way.
-不可能  -克里斯申  不
- It can't be. - Christian, no.
兹沃诺密尔看到他
Zvonomir saw him...
跟警察说话
..Talking to a cop.
什么
What?
在哪
Where?
他之前诬陷你告密
He pointed the finger at you.
你应该了结他
You should finish him.
不
No...
杀人只需要勇气
All it takes is character.
克里斯申  不
Christian, no.
约万
Jovan.
-但这是斯特凡  -约万
- But it's Stefan. - Jovan!
约万
Jovan.
他是个叛徒  约万
He's a rat, Jovan.
不不不  求你了  不
No, no, no, don't, please, no.
达沃  求你了  什么警察
Davor, please. What cop?
篮球场
The basketball arena.
你收了他的黑钱
You took his dirty money.
你个烂人
Your scam.
你还接受下赌吗
Hey, are you still taking bets?
我认识你吗
Do I know you from somewhere?
那  那人是警察吗
That...that guy is a cop?
达沃  求你了  你得相信我
Davor, please, you have to believe me.
-是克里斯申  你不能相信他  -别又来这套
- It's Christian, you can't trust him. - Not that again.
不不  他撒谎了
No, no, he's lied...
关于他的家庭  关于碧昂卡  一切都是谎言
..About his family, about Bianca, everything's a lie!
求你了  达沃  听我说
Please, Davor, listen to me.
我现在知道我在哪见过那个警察了
I know now where... where I've seen that cop before.
求你了  求你了  我能证明
Please, please, I can prove it.
就给我...
Just give me...
让他去
Let him go.